Brother Liu, it's been a while.
Brother Liu, please.
General Ning,
congratulations on your upcoming wedding.
Let's drink to that.
We are only enjoying tonight
because of this happy occasion.
Congratulations, General.
Indeed.
Why does the girl in the middle
look a bit like Keying?
Ning Yuanci
didn't even send me an invitation.
I'm coming whether he likes it or not.
Just watch me ruin
your engagement banquet.
Why is Xue Keying here?
I never sent her an invitation.
Young Master Chu
probably brought her here.
I remember
that painter named Chu
is your childhood sweetheart.
You misunderstand, General Ning.
Chu Qingyun and I
only knew each other as children.
We studied together at the academy
and stopped seeing each other long ago.
Keying, on the other hand,
has been quite close to him lately.
My Lady, tonight...
Have you barely eaten anything?
I have no appetite.
Then I will go find
something My Lady likes to eat.
Look!
The one dancing is my daughter.
How could she mingle
with the dancing girls?
How improper!
What do you know?
One must show their talents
when the time is right.
My daughter
is truly gifted
and as beautiful as a celestial being.
This is Lady Xue's favorite dish.
Remember
to serve it to the main table.
Give this to me.
Beautiful. What a wonderful dance.
I have a few friends over there.
I will go greet them and be right back.
General, please have
a good chat with Wan'er.
It's just an engagement banquet.
Is it worth
making it so grand?
Of course it is.
How come this date cake
tastes exactly like
the one at home?
Okay.
Lady Keying,
your dance just now
was incredibly graceful.
As graceful as a swan.
I am deeply impressed
and full of admiration.
You flatter me.
Mr. Chu,
go find Sister Wan while
Ning Yuanci is away.
Today is the engagement banquet
of Sister Wan
and General Ning.
It would be inappropriate
for me to do so.
It's just an engagement, not a wedding.
Besides, let me tell you,
Sister Wan doesn't like
Ning Yuanci at all.
And Ning Yuanci doesn't
care about her either.
Do you have the heart
to watch her sit there
all alone and sad?
Go comfort her.
That dancer sure knows how to flirt.
She must be trying to seduce Chu Qingyun,
the most talented scholar in the capital.
Who knows where this vixen came from.
Look at her,
barely wearing any clothes.
And showing off at General Ning's
engagement banquet.
Just listen to me.
Go, go.
Hurry up.
Pick up the fan for me.
It was just a bump.
Why are you so fierce?
What do you mean?
How dare a lowly dancer like you
bump into me!
Whose daughter are you?
General Ning,
My father is Commander Li,
who oversees conscription
under your command.
This shrew
struck me first just now.
I had no choice but to fight back.
Do you know
that the shrew you speak of
is the Second Lady of the Duke's Estate?
My fiancée
is her eldest sister.
It seems your father...
It will take a long time.
I'll teach you a lesson when we get home.
Tomorrow,
I will make him retire
and return to his hometown.
General Ning,
I know I was wrong.
I know how to act
in the face-slapping scene.
Who asked you to play
the hero saving the beauty?
What exactly are you trying to do
by putting on this show tonight?
I wasn't trying to do anything.
I'm just here for the fun.
Didn't I tell you that
except for marriage,
I can give you
whatever you want?
I didn't ask you for anything.
And I don't want to marry you either.
I just hope
you stay away from Xue Ruowan
so I can smoothly reach the finale.
The fireworks show starts now.
Don't interact with
that painter anymore.
I can still
treat you like I used to.
What did you say?
There are fireworks over there.
So beautiful.
Hurry up and grab a good spot.
Who told you to add a kissing scene?
My Lady,
are you alright? My Lady!
My Lady!
Somebody come!
My Lady has fainted!
Help!
Oh no. Xue Ruowan!
My Lady!
What is going on here?
Somebody help!
Xue Ruowan!
What happened?
My Lady suddenly fainted just now.
It seems she has been poisoned.
She's poisoned.
My Lady,
wake up! My Lady!
Wan'er.
Get some water, quick!
My Lady,
wake up!
Don't scare me.
My Lady.
Wan'er.
My Lady,
are you alright?
My Lady.
Summon the imperial physician!
She passed out again.
My Lady!
Mother,
come with me.
What is it?
Hurry!
What's wrong?
Did you do this?
Don't talk nonsense.
I just saw you
and Nanny Zhao acting suspiciously.
Dare you say
you have nothing to do
with these pastries?
I...
I just added a little cold-inducing poison
to the pastries.
I only wanted her
to catch a minor illness.
If she gets sick,
wouldn't you have a chance
to be with Ning Yuanci?
How many times have I told you?
Stop persecuting her.
Why are you acting like an NPC
inserted by the scriptwriter?
What?
I don't understand the nonsense
you're saying.
Let me tell you,
this cold-inducing poison
is not fatal.
If I wanted to kill that little wretch,
I would have done it long ago.
Why wait until now?
Then swear
you are telling the truth.
Fine.
I swear.
If I tell a single lie,
you can disown me,
and leave me uncared for
in my old age.
Is that enough?
Alright.
Madam Qin shouldn't have
the guts to kill someone in public.
What exactly is going on with Xue Ruowan?
Reporting to the Duke and Madam.
The imperial physician says
the Eldest Lady is severely poisoned
and is receiving acupuncture
and bloodletting.
Is it that serious?
Didn't you say it wouldn't be fatal?
Who
harmed my daughter?
H-He said
it's a deadly poison.
Then let's see
who poisoned
Xue Ruowan's pastries.
She served
these pastries herself.
Xue Ruowan was poisoned
right after eating them.
I...
Xiaolan...
I am here,
so you need not fear.
Tell us what you know.
You were the last person
to handle the pastries.